offlinesoftwares.net 2018-03-10

# Privacy Policy - Offline Softwares

Offline Softwares or [OfflineSoftwares.com](http://offlinesoftwares.com/) has a privacy policy for its users, visitors, subscribers or any person, entity or organization using it or its services for the purpose defined by Offline Softwares. Also, Privacy Policy or PII is for those who are concerned about how their information or data submitted here is being used. Here we, at Offline Softwares gather use, maintain and disclose information collected from users (each “User”) of the [ Offline Softwares](http://offlinesoftwares.com/) website(Site). This privacy policy applies to this website and all products and services offered by Offline Softwares.

 **Personal Identification Information(PII) we get:**

As appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your better experience. Moreover, we can get some technical details about your browser, your Internet, your ISP(Internet Service Provider), your operating system, and your device type.

 **Occasions of gathering information:**

We collect information from you when you are visiting, commenting or subscribing to our site or enter information on our site, OR Provide us with feedback on software or our services.

 **Use Your Information:**

We may use the information we collect from you in the following ways:

 **•**  To enhance your usage and to allow us to provide the type of content, software and service in which you are most interested.

 **•**  To improve our website in order to better serve you.

 **•**  To allow us to better service you in responding to your requests.

 **Protection of Your Information:**

Our website and dedicated Linux web servers are being scanned on a regularly scheduled basis for loopholes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We also do regular Malware Scanning with known CMS based, Control Panel based and Operating System based anti-malware programs, applications and add-ons. We do not use an SSL certificate strictly as we don’t collect any most sensitive private information like Credit Card Numbers or passwords but we still have flexible Firewall level SSL which is used when you submit your email address or similar identification information which you want to keep private.

 **What about ‘cookies’ use?**

Yes, we use cookies. Cookies are small size files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, cookies help us remember and process the improving practices for our users better future experience, including yours. These are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

 **We use cookies to:**

 **•** Maintain record and process the improving practices for our users better future experience, including yours.

 **•**  Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.

 **•**  Keep track of visits, interaction, and advertisements.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You can do this through your browser settings. As every browser has different GUI interface and design, but generally you can find this in your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies or just Google it. If you turn cookies off, some features may be disabled. It won’t affect the user’s experience but maybe your site experience becomes less efficient and may not function properly. However, you will still be able to visit, interact, comment or subscribe to site.

 **Third-party disclosure of PII:**

As your information is protected and is really protected so, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your info to other third parties.

 **Third-party links:**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or publish third-party links on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Advertising:**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to you by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. We will never display any Ads that will irritate our user like ‘pop-up ads’ at any cost. We will try to display ads in places where they should be placed like widgets area or between content where necessary.

 **Google Adsense:**

We may use Adsense for monetization of our website ads that will be served here by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their activities they do on Offline Softwares or other websites. DART uses “non-personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

 **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act):**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online. We do not specifically provide services to children under the age of 13 years.

 **CAN-SPAM Act:**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

 **We collect your email address in order to:**

 **•**  Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

 **To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM, we agree to the following:**

 **  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can do this using instruction given usually at the end of mail or you can email us at:  **

and we will promptly remove you from  **ALL**  correspondence.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy:**

Offline Softwares has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and will try to inform all returning users such as subscribers etc. But for both visitor and subscriber, you acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of changes and we are only responsible to make it available online on our website before it comes to action.

 **Your Acceptance of These Terms:**

By using [Offline Softwares](http://offlinesoftwares.com/), you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree with this policy or policy update, please do not use Offline Softwares with immediate effect. Your continued use of the Offline Softwares following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **If you still have queries about privacy policy you can[Contact Us](http://offlinesoftwares.com/contact-us/).**
